Ancient evil has come to feed.
Wyvern is a fantasy, science fiction, tv movie
film directed by Steven R. Monroe.
The residents of a small Alaskan town find themselves under attack by a
flying reptile known in medieval mythology as a Wyvern.
It has thawed from its ancient slumber by melting
icecaps caused by global warming.
Jake Suttner, played by Nick Chinlund.
Clair, played by Erin Karpluk.
Haas, played by Barry Corbin.
Colonel Travis Sherman, played by Don S. Davis.
Deputy Barnes, played by Elaine Miles.
Hampton, played by Tinsel Korey.
Wyvern, also known as Dragon, is a 2009 Canadian-American made-for-television horror film produced by RHI
Entertainment that premiered in the United States on the Syfy Channel on January 31, 2009.
Written by Jason Bourque and directed by Steven R.
Monroe, Wyvern is the fifteenth film in the Maneater film series,
produced under an agreement with Sci Fi Pictures.
The film stars Nick Chinlund as Jake Suttner, a trucker who must stop a wyvern
from eating the residents in the small town of Beaver Mills, Alaska.
In Japan, it is titled Jurassic Predator.
The film explores themes of global warming, alaska, dragon, wyvern.
The tone is thought_provoking.